<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Name of the application.
{{Identical|Wikipedia}}</string>
  <string name="app_name_beta">Name of the beta version of the application.
{{Identical|Wikipedia Beta}}</string>
  <string name="app_name_alpha">Name of the alpha version of the application.</string>
  <string name="yes">Affirmative answer to a dialog box.
{{Identical|Yes}}</string>
  <string name="no">Negative answer to a dialog box.
{{Identical|No}}</string>
  <string name="acra_report_dialog_title">Title of the dialog that pops up when the app crashes, asking user to send a report</string>
  <string name="acra_report_dialog_text">Text asking the user to send us a crash report</string>
  <string name="acra_report_dialog_comment">Label for text box asking user to tell us what they were doing when the app crashed</string>
  <string name="search_hint">Placeholder text for the search textbox</string>
  <string name="history_activity_title">Title for the screen that shows history of articles you have read.
{{Identical|History}}</string>
  <string name="nav_item_history">Text in navigation sidebar that when tapped leads to the History screen.
{{Identical|History}}</string>
  <string name="error_network_error">Error message shown when network cannot be reached when loading a page</string>
  <string name="search_network_error">Error message shown when network cannot be reached when searching. Tapping the message retries the search.</string>
  <string name="page_error_retry">Text for button that retries page loading when tapped.
{{Identical|Retry}}</string>
  <string name="menu_clear_all_history">Menu item text for clearing your reading history.
{{Identical|Clear history}}</string>
  <string name="menu_clear_all_bookmarks">Menu item text for clearing bookmarks</string>
  <string name="menu_clear_all_saved_pages">Clear is an imperative verb. This is an action that clears all saved pages.</string>
  <string name="page_does_not_exist_error">Text shown when the requested page does not exist</string>
  <string name="nav_item_today">Text in navigation sidebar that when tapped leads to the Main Page.
{{Identical|Today}}</string>
  <string name="dialog_title_clear_history">Title for dialog box asking if you want to clear your reading history.</string>
  <string name="saved_pages_activity_title">Title for screen that shows list of saved pages.
{{Identical|Saved page}}</string>
  <string name="nav_item_saved_pages">Text in navigation sidebar that when tapped leads to the saved pages.
{{Identical|Saved page}}</string>
  <string name="menu_update_all_saved_pages">Menu item (icon) in saved pages screen to update all saved pages.
{{Identical|Update saved page}}</string>
  <string name="menu_update_selected_saved_pages">Menu item (icon) in saved pages screen to update selected saved pages.
{{Identical|Update saved page}}</string>
  <string name="dialog_prompt_refresh_all_saved_pages">Prompt before updating all saved pages</string>
  <string name="toast_saved_page_refreshed">Small toast (popup) message saying that all saved pages were updated</string>
  <string name="menu_save_page">Menu item text for saving the currently active page.
{{Identical|Save page}}</string>
  <string name="menu_share_page">Menu item text for sharing the currently active page. Uses the build-in Android sharing functionality, so translate it the same way as the operating system does.
{{Identical|Share}}</string>
  <string name="share_via">Dialog title text for Share list.

The Share list contains the following menu items (localized):
* Mail
* Message</string>
  <string name="dialog_title_clear_saved_pages">Title for dialog box asking if you want to clear all of your saved pages</string>
  <string name="dialog_message_clear_saved_pages">Message for dialog box asking if you want to clear all your saved pages</string>
  <string name="toast_saving_page">Small toast (popup) message saying that a page is being saved for offline reading</string>
  <string name="toast_saved_page">Small toast (popup) message saying that a page has been saved for offline reading.

See also:
* {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-toast saved page missing images}}</string>
  <string name="toast_saved_page_missing_images">Small toast (popup) message saying that not all images of a saved page could be saved.

See also:
* {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-toast saved page}}</string>
  <string name="toast_save_page_failed">Small toast (popup) message saying that a page has failed to be saved</string>
  <string name="toast_refresh_saved_page">Small toast (popup) message saying that a saved page is being refreshed</string>
  <string name="delete_selected_saved_pages">Menu item text for deleting the currently selected saved pages
{{Identical|Delete}}</string>
  <string name="toast_saved_page_deleted">Small toast (popup) message saying that the selected saved pages have been deleted</string>
  <string name="saved_pages_search_list_hint">Hint for textbox that searches list of items in saved pages as user types.
      {{Identical|Search}}</string>
  <string name="saved_pages_search_empty_message">Message shown when no saved pages were found that match the user\'s query.</string>
  <string name="nearby_activity_title">Title for Nearby activity (top of screen)
{{Identical|Nearby}}</string>
  <string name="nav_item_nearby">Entry in nav drawer for Nearby feature
{{Identical|Nearby}}</string>
  <string name="menu_update_nearby">Action bar item to refresh list of nearby pages</string>
  <string name="nearby_empty_title">Title line for message when no nearby pages were found</string>
  <string name="nearby_empty_message">Message details when no nearby pages were found</string>
  <string name="nearby_distance_in_meters">Distance to the place mentioned in the nearby page in meters. Please leave the %d as is. It represents an integer decimal number up to 999.</string>
  <string name="nearby_distance_in_kilometers">Distance to the place mentioned in the nearby page in kilometers. Please leave the %.2f as is. It represents a floating point number with 2 digits after the decimal point.</string>
  <string name="nearby_distance_in_feet">Distance to the place mentioned in the nearby page in feet. Please leave the %d as is. It represents an integer decimal number up to 999.</string>
  <string name="nearby_distance_in_miles">Distance to the place mentioned in the nearby page in miles. Please leave the %.2f as is. It represents a floating point number with 2 digits after the decimal point.</string>
  <string name="nearby_no_network">Error message when there was a network error while displaying nearby articles.</string>
  <string name="nearby_server_error">Error message when the app could not get list of nearby places from the server.</string>
  <string name="nearby_no_location">Error message when the app could not get a location from any location provider (network or GPS).</string>
  <string name="nearby_dialog_goto_settings">Dialog text that tells the user that Location updates are not enabled on the device, and asks if the user wants to go to the Settings page on the device where they can enable Location updates.</string>
  <string name="nearby_set_metric">Menu item for displaying distances in metric units (meters and kilometers).</string>
  <string name="nearby_set_imperial">Menu item for displaying distances in imperial units (feet and miles).</string>
  <string name="last_updated_text">Message in footer of article indicating when the article was last updated. \'%s\' is substituted with the appropriately formatted human-readable timestamp, such as \"seven days ago\".</string>
  <string name="content_license_html">HTML specifying license of the Wiki and link to appropriate CC page</string>
  <string name="edit_save_action_license_logged_in">HTML specifying Terms of Use and CC license before saving edits</string>
  <string name="edit_save_action_license_anon">HTML specifying Terms of Use and CC license and a log link before saving edits, only when the user has not logged in. Please do not change the href=\'https://#login\' part of the message.</string>
  <string name="preference_title_language">Title for preference in settings screen for setting which language wikipedia to use.</string>
  <string name="preference_summary_language">A label for a setting that chooses the language in which the content of Wikipedia will be shown.</string>
  <string name="preference_languages_filter_hint">Placeholder text for the textbox that when typed filters list of language wikipedias from which user can pick a language to use.
{{Identical|Search}}</string>
  <string name="langlinks_filter_hint">{{Identical|Search}}</string>
  <string name="menu_other_languages">Menu item for showing list of languages in which this article is available.
{{Identical|Otherlanguages}}</string>
  <string name="langlinks_error_retry">Text for button that when tapped retries fetching the list of languages in which the current article is available.
{{Identical|Retry}}</string>
  <string name="langlinks_empty">Message shown when the user requested a list of languages in which the current article is available, but the current article is not available in any other language</string>
  <string name="langlinks_no_match">Message shown when the user requested a list of languages in which the current article is available, and filtered that list using a search, but their search query does not match any of the other languages the article is available in.</string>
  <string name="settings_activity_title">Title for settings screen.
{{Identical|Settings}}</string>
  <string name="langlinks_activity_title">Menu item that shows user list of languages the current article is available in.
{{Identical|Otherlanguages}}</string>
  <string name="menu_save_changes">{{Identical|Save changes}}</string>
  <string name="edit_section_error_retry">Text for button that retries page loading when tapped.
{{Identical|Retry}}</string>
  <string name="dialog_saving_in_progress">Text for progress dialog shown when an edit save is in progress.
{{Identical|Saving}}</string>
  <string name="edit_saved_successfully">Small toast (popup) message saying that the edit was successful</string>
  <string name="dialog_message_edit_failed">Message for dialog box specifying that an edit save had failed</string>
  <string name="dialog_message_edit_failed_retry">Button text to retry a failed edit save.
{{Identical|Retry}}</string>
  <string name="dialog_message_edit_failed_cancel">Button text to cancel retrying a failed edit save.
{{Identical|Cancel}}</string>
  <string name="dialog_message_leaving_edit">Message for dialog box shown to users when they click on a link in an edit preview, informing them that if they leave the edit then they may lose their changes.</string>
  <string name="dialog_message_leaving_edit_leave">Button text for choosing to leave the edit workflow when the user clicks on a link in preview.
{{Identical|Leave}}</string>
  <string name="dialog_message_leaving_edit_stay">Button text for choosing to stay inside edit workflow when the user clicks on a link in preview.
{{Identical|Stay}}</string>
  <string name="menu_show_toc">Menu item text for showing the Table of Contents for the current article.
{{Identical|Table of contents}}</string>
  <string name="search_no_results_found">Message shown to user when no search results are found for a string</string>
  <string name="edit_section_captcha_message">A label for the CAPTCHA screen.</string>
  <string name="edit_section_captcha_hint">A call to action to write the CAPTCHA string.</string>
  <string name="title_captcha">A call to action to write the CAPTCHA string.</string>
  <string name="edit_section_captcha_reload">Call to action. \"Tap\" is imperative verb, \"touch the touchscreen\".</string>
  <string name="edit_saved_page_refresh">Dialog text that asks the user if they want to refresh the saved page, so that editing would be enabled.</string>
  <string name="nav_item_login">{{Identical|Log in}}</string>
  <string name="login_username_hint">{{Identical|Username}}</string>
  <string name="login_password_hint">{{Identical|Password}}</string>
  <string name="login_password_show_check">Used as label for the checkbox to mask/unmask password.</string>
  <string name="menu_login">{{Identical|Log in}}</string>
  <string name="login_activity_title">Used as window title.</string>
  <string name="login_in_progress_dialog_message">A bubble that describes the in-progress action.</string>
  <string name="login_error_wrong_password">An error message.
{{Related|Wikipedia-android-strings-login error}}</string>
  <string name="login_error_wrong_username">Used as error message if the specified user does not exist.
{{Related|Wikipedia-android-strings-login error}}</string>
  <string name="login_success_toast">A bubble that appears after logging in.</string>
  <string name="login_error_blocked">Used as alert message.
{{Related|Wikipedia-android-strings-login error}}</string>
  <string name="login_error_throttled">An error message.
{{Related|Wikipedia-android-strings-login error}}</string>
  <string name="login_error_unknown">Used as alert message.
{{Related|Wikipedia-android-strings-login error}}</string>
  <string name="login_error_no_network">Used as alert message.
{{Related|Wikipedia-android-strings-login error}}</string>
  <string name="nav_item_logout">{{Identical|Log out}}</string>
  <string name="preference_title_logout">{{Identical|Log out}}</string>
  <string name="preference_summary_logout">Summary of what logging out means.</string>
  <string name="preference_summary_notloggedin">{{Identical|Not logged in}}</string>
  <string name="toast_logout_complete">Toast popup message notifying the user that they have been logged out.
{{Identical|Logged out}}</string>
  <string name="saved_pages_empty_title">Used in \"Saved pages\" page if there are no saved pages to show.</string>
  <string name="saved_pages_empty_message">Brief explanation of what saved pages are, and their benefits.</string>
  <string name="history_empty_title">Used in \"Browsing history\" page if there is nothing to show.</string>
  <string name="history_empty_message">Brief explanation that there are currently no History entries to look at. Just to fill an empty screen. This usually happens when a user just deleted history entries.</string>
  <string name="delete_selected_history">Menu item text for deleting the currently selected history entries
{{Identical|Delete}}</string>
  <string name="wp_stylized">A stylized string saying \"Wikipedia\". Used before wp_tag_line if no image representation exists. Usually the first and last characters are within big tags, if this fits the Wikipedia logo in your language.</string>
  <string name="wp_tag_line">The Wikipedia slogan. The second line of https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/Wikimedia#mediaviewer/File:Wikipedia-logo-en.png. You may be able to find one under https://commons.wikimedia.org/wiki/Wikipedia/2.0.</string>
  <string name="skip">A button or text link to trigger skipping something, like closing the current screen without doing anything.
{{Identical|Skip}}</string>
  <string name="create_account_username_hint">{{Identical|Username}}</string>
  <string name="create_account_password_hint">{{Identical|Password}}</string>
  <string name="menu_create_account">{{Identical|Create account}}</string>
  <string name="login_create_account_link">Link text on Login screen to go to Create Account screen.

See also:
* {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-create account login link}}</string>
  <string name="create_account_login_link">Link text on Create Account screen to go to Login screen.

See also:
* {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-login create account link}}</string>
  <string name="create_account_activity_title">{{Identical|Create account}}</string>
  <string name="edit_section_activity_title">Title for screen where user is editing a single section.</string>
  <string name="create_account_password_repeat_hint">{{Identical|Repeat password}}</string>
  <string name="create_account_passwords_mismatch_error">{{Identical|Passwords do not match}}</string>
  <string name="create_account_username_exists_error">Used as error message on creating a user account.</string>
  <string name="create_account_noname_error">Used as an error message during account creation when the account creation failed because username that was provided is invalid.</string>
  <string name="create_account_invalid_email_error">Used as an error message during account creation when the account creation failed because the email that was provided is invalid.</string>
  <string name="create_account_password_too_short_error">Used as an error message during account creation when the account creation failed because the password that was entered is too short.</string>
  <string name="create_account_blocked_anon_error">Used as an error message during account creation when the account creation failed because their IP address is blocked.

See also:
* {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-create account blocked error}}</string>
  <string name="create_account_blocked_error">Used as an error message during account creation when the the account creation failed because their account is blocked.

See also:
* {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-create account blocked anon error}}</string>
  <string name="create_account_password_name_match_error">Used as an error message during account creation when the the account creation failed because the username and password provided are the same.</string>
  <string name="create_account_no_network">Message shown when the network is unavailable during account creation</string>
  <string name="create_account_next">Button text on Create Account screen to go \"next\" (to CAPTCHA).
{{Identical|Next}}</string>
  <string name="create_account_button">Button text on Create Account screen to go start creating the account (may also go to a CAPTCHA screen first).
{{Identical|Create account}}</string>
  <string name="preferences_general_heading">Preferences general heading.
{{Identical|General}}</string>
  <string name="zero_charged_verbiage">Text for toast connoting that Wikipedia Zero status went to OFF</string>
  <string name="zero_charged_verbiage_extended">Extended text describing that further usage of the app may in fact incur data charges because Wikipedia Zero is off.</string>
  <string name="zero_search_hint">Searchbar hint incorporting notion that user is searching via Wikipedia Zero so it is free</string>
  <string name="zero_warn_when_leaving">Settings label for option for warning a Wikipedia Zero user if tapping on an external link</string>
  <string name="zero_warn_when_leaving_summary">Lengthy explanation of Wikipedia Zero for settings screen</string>
  <string name="zero_webpage_title">Link title for the Wikipedia Zero FAQ for the app</string>
  <string name="zero_webpage_url">Not to be translated</string>
  <string name="zero_wikipedia_zero_heading">Settings heading for Wikipedia Zero.
{{Identical|Wikipedia Zero}}</string>
  <string name="zero_interstitial_title">Dialog title text to inform Wikipedia Zero user that the user is about to leave the app for an external link</string>
  <string name="zero_interstitial_leave_app">Dialog text to ask Wikipedia Zero user whether the user wants to continue to an external site where standard data charges may apply</string>
  <string name="zero_interstitial_continue">Dialog button text for Wikipedia Zero user to leave the app for an external site where standard data charges may apply.</string>
  <string name="zero_interstitial_cancel">Dialog button text for Wikipedia Zero to stay in the app and thereby avoid leaving the app for an external site where standard data charges may apply.
{{Identical|Stay here}}</string>
  <string name="zero_learn_more">Message of a dialog shown the first time Wikipedia Zero mode is On.</string>
  <string name="zero_learn_more_learn_more">Dialog button text for Wikipedia Zero user to learn more about Wikipedia Zero at the Wikipedia Zero FAQ for the app.
{{Identical|Read more}}</string>
  <string name="zero_learn_more_dismiss">Dialog button text for Wikipedia Zero user to dismiss the prompt about visiting the Wikipedia Zero FAQ for the app</string>
  <string name="zero_settings">Generic Settings heading for Wikipedia Zero.
{{Identical|Settings}}</string>
  <string name="zero_settings_devmode">Prerelease label text for enabling Wikipedia Zero Devmode to enable Wikipedia Zero support</string>
  <string name="zero_settings_devmode_summary">Prerelease explanation text explaining that Wikipedia Zero Devmode on means that Wikipedia Zero detection will be turned on</string>
  <string name="create_account_logging_in">{{Identical|Logging in}}</string>
  <string name="send_feedback">Text to show for link used for sending feedback about the app.</string>
  <string name="edit_summary_guide_text">An imperative message, which appears after starting to save an edit.</string>
  <string name="edit_summary_hint">{{Identical|Edit summary}}</string>
  <string name="nav_item_random">{{Identical|Random}}
Shown in left navigation. Tapping it produces a random page.</string>
  <string name="random_progress">Message shown in progress popup dialog while waiting for a random article to be fetched</string>
  <string name="create_account_account_created_toast">Message shown in a small toast when account creation is successful.
* {{msg-mw|Accountcreatedtext|message}}</string>
  <string name="user_contribs_more_action">Text shown as a button at the end of lists that let the user load more items.
{{Identical|Load more}}</string>
  <string name="activity_my_contributions_title">Title for screen showing list of edits by current user.
{{Identical|Contribution}}</string>
  <string name="nav_item_my_contributions">Text for item in nav menu that when tapped shows list of edits made by the user.
{{Identical|Contribution}}</string>
  <string name="edit_save_action_login">Title of action that takes user to login screen so they can login before saving an edit</string>
  <string name="edit_save_action_ip">Title of action that lets the user save the current edit anonymously
{{Identical|Save anonymously}}</string>
  <string name="edit_save_action_login_description">Description for action that lets the user save the current edit anonymously.

See also:
* {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-edit save action ip description}}</string>
  <string name="edit_save_action_ip_description">Description for action that takes user to login screen so they can login before saving an edit.

See also:
* {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-edit save action login description}}</string>
  <string name="preference_title_eventlogging_opt_in">Title of preference that when checked enables data collection of user behavior.</string>
  <string name="preference_summary_eventlogging_opt_in">Description of preference that when checked enables data collection of user behavior.</string>
  <string name="editing_error_spamblacklist">An error message, which appears after trying to save a page with blacklisted links. The single string parameter %s for this message gets substituted with the blocked domain.</string>
  <string name="history_search_list_hint">Hint for textbox that searches list of items in browsing history as user types.
{{Identical|Search}}</string>
  <string name="history_search_empty_message">Message shown when no history items were found that match the user\'s query.</string>
  <string name="error_can_not_process_link">Message shown in a toast when the app encounters a link it can not process.</string>
  <string name="page_protected_autoconfirmed">Message shown to users when editing a semi-protected page</string>
  <string name="page_protected_sysop">Message shown to users when editing a fully protected page</string>
  <string name="page_protected_other">Message shown to users when editing a page that is protected with a custom level of protection. %s refers to the name of the protection level. Examples include \'templateeditor\' on enwiki.</string>
  <string name="page_protected_can_not_edit">Message in dialog box telling the user that they can not edit this page because it is protected.</string>
  <string name="page_protected_can_not_edit_title">Title of dialog box telling the user that they can not edit this page because it is protected.</string>
  <string name="more_item_preferences">Used as menu item in the nav menu to go to the Settings screen.

The title for the Settings screen is {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-more activity title}}.

See screenshot [[commons:File:Wikipedia Android app menu open.png]]
{{Identical|More}}</string>
  <string name="more_activity_title">Title at the top of the More (Settings) screen.

See also:
* {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-more item preferences}} - menu item to come to this screen
{{Identical|More}}</string>
  <string name="about_description">Summary of the preference item to show the About screen.</string>
  <string name="privacy_policy_description">{{Identical|Privacy policy}}</string>
  <string name="preference_title_version">Text for the preference item that shows the app version number.
{{Identical|Version}}</string>
  <string name="about_libraries_heading">Heading for section that lists the libraries that have been used in the app</string>
  <string name="about_contributors_heading">Heading for section that lists the people who have contributed to the app.
{{Identical|Contributor}}</string>
  <string name="about_translators_heading">Heading for section that gives credit to translatewiki transators.
{{Identical|Translator}}</string>
  <string name="about_translators_translatewiki">Credit given to translatewiki translators.

{{doc-important|Please don\'t translate the link and the site title.}}</string>
  <string name="about_wmf">Text and link specifying that this app was developed by the Wikimedia Foundation</string>
  <string name="about_activity_title">{{Identical|About}}</string>
  <string name="edit_unchanged">Message displayed when the user tries to save a page when no modifications were made.</string>
  <string name="edit_abandon_confirm">Prompt for the user to abandon any changes that were made during editing.</string>
  <string name="user_blocked_from_editing_title">{{Identical|Blocked}}</string>
  <string name="user_logged_in_blocked_from_editing">Message shown in dialog box to users who are blocked from editing when they attempt to save an edit</string>
  <string name="user_anon_blocked_from_editing">Message shown in dialog box to users who are blocked from editing based on their IP address</string>
  <string name="edit_how_page_improved">Question that asks the user how they improved the article after editing</string>
  <string name="edit_next">Button text to go \"next\" after the editing screen to the preview screen.
{{Identical|Next}}</string>
  <string name="edit_done">Button text to finish editing and save the changes.
{{Identical|Save}}</string>
  <string name="edit_preview">Header text to show above the preview of the edited article.
{{Identical|Preview}}</string>
  <string name="edit_summary_tag_typo">Clickable summary tag for fixing a typo</string>
  <string name="edit_summary_tag_grammar">Clickable summary tag for fixing grammar</string>
  <string name="edit_summary_tag_links">Clickable summary tag for adding link(s)</string>
  <string name="edit_summary_tag_other">Clickable summary tag for a custom/other edit summary text.
{{Identical|Other}}</string>
  <string name="edit_summary_tag_other_hint">Hint (input field placeholder) for the user to write a custom summary of edits</string>
  <string name="find_in_page">Menu item for invoking Find in page on current page plus the hint text for the Find in page control</string>
  <string name="find_next">Text for button that finds the next occurrence of a search term.
{{Identical|Find next}}</string>
  <string name="find_previous">Text for button that finds the previous occurrence of a search term</string>
  <string name="find_close">Text for button that closes the find-in-page bar</string>
  <string name="error_network_error_try_again">Message shown when encountering network connection issues that may be corrected by simply retrying.</string>
  <string name="saved_pages_update_all_error_retry">Label for button shown in error dialog when updating saved pages fails that lets user try again.
{{Identical|Retry}}</string>
  <string name="saved_pages_update_all_error_message">Message for error dialog shown when updating pages fails</string>
  <string name="saved_pages_progress_title">Title for progress dialog shown when updating saved pages</string>
  <string name="saved_pages_refresh_pages_complete">Toast message shown when a user initiated \"update save pages\" action has been completed</string>
  <string name="menu_page_saved">Menu item that says that the current page has been saved.</string>
  <string name="menu_refresh_saved_page">Menu item for refreshing the saved page that is currently shown.
{{Identical|Refresh page}}</string>
  <string name="abusefilter_title_warn">Message that warns the user that their edit may be unconstructive, and asks if they want to continue saving it.</string>
  <string name="abusefilter_title_disallow">Message that informs the user that their edit is not allowed, and that the user must go back and modify the edit.</string>
  <string name="abusefilter_text_warn">Explanation of why the edit may be flagged as unconstructive: Typing in all caps, Blanking articles or Spamming, Irrelevant external links or images, Repeating characters</string>
  <string name="abusefilter_text_disallow">Explanation of why the edit was not allowed: potentially unconstructive, or potential vandalism.</string>
  <string name="dialog_page_issues">Dialog title for page/article issues list.
{{Identical|Page issue}}</string>
  <string name="button_page_issues">Label for button that shows the Page issues dialog.
{{Identical|Page issue}}</string>
  <string name="menu_themechooser">Menu item for choosing text size and color scheme</string>
  <string name="text_size_select">Label that describes text size selection</string>
  <string name="color_theme_select">Label that describes color theme selection
{{Identical|Theme}}</string>
  <string name="color_theme_light">Button label for Light color theme</string>
  <string name="color_theme_dark">Button label for Dark color theme</string>
  <string name="page_similar_titles">Button label for showing a list of similar titles (disambiguation) for the current page</string>
  <string name="search_within_pages">Button label for full-text searching within pages for the current search term</string>
  <string name="search_no_results">Label that tells the user that no results were found. The \"%s\" symbol is replaced with the phrase that was searched.</string>
  <string name="search_did_you_mean">Label that gives the user a suggestion for a better search term, instead of the one that the user gave. The \"%s\" symbol is replaced with the suggestion.</string>
  <string name="search_results_title">Title of the dialog box that contains search results.
{{Identical|Search results}}</string>
  <string name="search_error_retry">Button label for retrying the search after a network error.
{{Identical|Retry}}</string>
  <string name="search_redirect_title">Label that tells the user that the search result is actually a redirect from another page, specified by the \"%s\" symbol.</string>
  <string name="search_recent_header">Label at the top of the list of recent searches that the user performed.</string>
  <string name="button_clear_all_recent_searches">Button hint for clearing search history;  visible when in search mode.</string>
  <string name="clear_recent_searches_confirm">Dialog message that asks if the user really wants to clear the search history.</string>
  <string name="search_titles_button">Button label for searching page title matches.
{{Identical|Title}}</string>
  <string name="search_full_button">Button label for searching the full text of pages.</string>
  <string name="toc_hint">Instructions how to open the Table of Contents drawer. In left-to-right languages (most) this means to swipe left from the right edge. In right-to-left languages (Hebrew, Arabic, etc.) this means to swipe right from the left edge. \'\'\'In RTL languages\'\'\' please adjust the text to say right swipe instead of left swipe.</string>
  <string name="toc_know_it">Button text to acknowledge instructions for opening Table of Contents drawer.</string>
  <string name="error_browser_not_found">Toast message shown when we try to open an external browser but none seems to be installed.</string>
  <string name="table_close">{{Identical|Close}}</string>
  <string name="app_store_description">Description of the app as put up on the Google Play Store</string>
  <string name="alpha_update_notification_title">Title for notification when new alpha update is available.

Followed by {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-alpha update notification text}}.</string>
  <string name="alpha_update_notification_text">Text for notification when new alpha update is available.

Preceded by {{msg-wm|Wikipedia-android-strings-alpha update notification title}}.</string>
  <string name="dialog_close_description">Button description for the close image button. The text is mainly for screen readers.
{{Identical|Close}}</string>
  <string name="preference_title_show_images">Preference title for selecting whether images are loaded in pages</string>
  <string name="preference_summary_show_images">Description of the preference for whether images are loaded, mentioning that this setting should be disabled if the user\'s internet connection is slow, or if their data plan is limited or restricted.</string>
</resources>
